Guide to the E. L. Wolven Glass Plate Negative Collection, 1897-1944
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IV. Graduation and Reunion, 1900-1942
  - Class Day Activities
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1935 Jun (Box 46 [Package41_004])
    - Class Day — Class of 1937 Daisy Chain, 1935 Jun (Box 76 [227_22])
    - Class Day — Class of 1937 Daisy Chain, 1935 Jun (Box 23 [package117c])
    - Class Day — Class of 1937 Daisy Chain, 1935 Jun (Box 23 [package117f])
    - Class Day — Class of 1937 Daisy Chain, 1935 Jun (Box 23 [package117g])
    - Class Day — Class of 1937 Daisy Chain, 1935 Jun (Box 26 [package148c])
    - Class Day — Class of 1937 Daisy Chain, 1935 Jun (Box 26 [package148d])
    - Class Day — Class of 1937 Daisy chain, 1935 Jun (Box 46 [Package41_003])
    - Class Day — Class of 1937 Daisy chain, 1935 Jun (Box 46 [Package41_005])
    - Class Day — Class of 1937 Daisy chain, 1935 Jun (Box 46 [Package41_009])
    - Class Day — Class of 1937 Daisy chain, 1935 Jun (Box 46 [Package41_011])
    - Class Day — Seniors marching into Class Day exercises, 1935 Jun (Box 23 [package117b])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1936 Jun (Box 79/80 [233_16])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1936 Jun (Box 79/80 [233_24])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1936 Jun (Box 82 [238_22])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1936 Jun (Box 40/41 [Box275_005])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1936 Jun (Box 6 [Package022_001])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1936 Jun (Box 6 [Package022_002])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1936 Jun (Box 6 [Package022_003])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1936 Jun (Box 6 [Package022_004])
    - Class Day — Class of 1938 Daisy Chain on the steps of Students' Building, 1936 Jun (Box 68 [212_01])
    - Class Day — Class of 1938 Daisy Chain on the steps of Students' Building, 1936 Jun (Box 1 [Package004_001])
    - Class Day — Class of 1938 Daisy Chain on the steps of Students' Building, 1936 Jun (Box 1 [Package004_002])
    - Class Day — Class of 1938 Daisy Chain on the steps of Students' Building, 1936 Jun (Box 1 [Package004_003])
    - Class Day — Class of 1938 Daisy Chain on the steps of Students' Building, 1936 Jun (Box 1 [Package004_004])
    - Class Day — Class of 1938 Daisy Chain on the steps of Students' Building, 1936 Jun (Box 1 [Package004_005])
    - Class Day — Students chatting, 1936 Jun (Box 6 [Package022_005])
    - Class Day — Class of 1935 Daisy Chain on the steps of Students' Building, 1937 Jun (Box 68 [212_12])
    - Class Day — Class of 1935 Daisy Chain on the steps of Students' Building, 1937 Jun (Box 68 [212_22])
    - Class Day — Class of 1940 Daisy Chain, 1938 Jun (Box 76 [227_20])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1939 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_016])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1939 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_017])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1939 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_019])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1939 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_020])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1939 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_021])
    - Class Day — Class of 1941 Daisy Chain, 1939 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_014])
    - Class Day — Class of 1941 Daisy Chain, 1939 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_018])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1940 Jun (Box 61 [199_02])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1940 Jun (Box 61 [199_03])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1940 Jun (Box 61 [199_14])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1940 Jun (Box 61 [199_15])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1940 Jun (Box 61 [199_16])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1940 Jun (Box 61 [199_21])
    - Class Day — Class of 1942 Daisy Chain, 1940 Jun (Box 61 [199_01])
    - Class Day — Class of 1942 Daisy Chain, 1940 Jun (Box 61 [199_20])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1941 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_010])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1941 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_011])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1941 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_012])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1941 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_013])
    - Class Day — Class of 1943 Daisy Chain, 1941 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_005])
    - Class Day — Class of 1943 Daisy Chain, 1941 Jun (Box 99 [Box260_015])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1942 Jun (Box 61 [199_05])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1942 Jun (Box 61 [199_06])
    - Class Day — Class Day exercises, 1942 Jun (Box 61 [199_18])
    - Class Day — Class of 1944 Daisy Chain, 1942 Jun (Box 61 [199_07])
    - Class Day — Class of 1944 Daisy Chain, 1942 Jun (Box 61 [199_11])
  - Commencement
    - Commencement — Copy photograph of a group of women in line outside Rockefeller Hall, possibly for commencement or reunion, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package018_016])
    - Commencement — Copy photograph of students in commencement dresses entering the Chapel, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package018_020])
    - Commencement — Copy photograph of students walking at commencement, 1900-1910 (Box 28 [package156j])
    - Commencement — Commencement, held to the side of Main Building, 1900-1915 (Box 35/36 [Box268_024])
    - Commencement — Class of 1909 climbing the stage at commencement, 1909 Jun (Box 80/81 [235_24])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1915, 1915 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_020])
    - Commencement — Anne Thorp (VC 1917) leading the Class of 1915 in the commencement procession, 1915 Jun 9 (Box 35 [Box267_018])
    - Commencement — Dean Ella McCaleb at Commencement, 1918 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_017])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, including President MacCracken and board chair Charles M. Pratt, 1918 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_007])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession. Caroline Furness is in the center facing the camera, 1918 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_008])
    - Commencement — Julie Chamberlain (VC 1920) leading the senior procession at Commencement, 1918 Jun (Box 44 [Box280_016])
    - Commencement — Julie Chamberlain (VC 1920) leading the senior procession at Commencement, 1918 Jun (Box 8 [Package034_005])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1918 at Commencement, 1918 Jun (Box 33/34 [Box265_022])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1918 at Commencement, 1918 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_009])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1918 at Commencement, 1918 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_018])
    - Commencement — Class of 1920 passing diplomas at commencement, 1920 Jun (Box 33/34 [Box265_015])
    - Commencement — Class of 1920 passing diplomas at commencement, 1920 Jun (Box 33/34 [Box265_017])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1920, 1920 Jun (Box 90/91 [Box249_001])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1920, 1920 Jun (Box 90/91 [Box249_003])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1920, 1920 Jun (Box 90/91 [Box249_004])
    - Commencement — Sophomore marshal Janet Graham (VC 1922) with a member of the Class of 1920, 1920 Jun (Box 42 [Box277_013])
    - Commencement — Sophomore marshal Janet Graham (VC 1922) with Professor Herbert Mills and a member of the Class of 1920, 1920 Jun (Box 33/34 [Box265_016])
    - Commencement — Alumnae in the commencement procession, 1921 Jun (Box 73/74 [222_02])
    - Commencement — Alumnae in the commencement procession, 1921 Jun (Box 73/74 [222_25])
    - Commencement — Class of 1921 in the commencement procession, 1921 Jun (Box 1 [Package008_001])
    - Commencement — Class of 1921 in the commencement procession, 1921 Jun (Box 7 [Package030_002])
    - Commencement — Class of 1921 passing diplomas at commencement, 1921 Jun (Box 7 [Package029_003])
    - Commencement — Class of 1921 passing diplomas at commencement, 1921 Jun (Box 7 [Package030_005])
    - Commencement — Class of 1921 passing diplomas at commencement, 1921 Jun (Box 10 [Package079_005])
    - Commencement — Class of 1921 passing diplomas at commencement, 1921 Jun (Box 10 [Package079_007])
    - Commencement — Crowd at Commencement, 1921 Jun (Box 3 [Package015_003])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, including President MacCracken and board chair Daniel Smiley, 1921 Jun (Box 4 [Package020_001])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, including President MacCracken and board chair Daniel Smiley, 1921 Jun (Box 10 [Package079_001])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, including President MacCracken and board chair Daniel Smiley, 1921 Jun (Box 10 [Package079_004])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees leaving the Chapel after Commencement, 1921 Jun (Box 7 [Package029_005])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees leaving the Chapel after Commencement, including President MacCracken and board chair Daniel Smiley, 1921 Jun (Box 10 [Package079_003])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees leaving the Chapel after Commencement, including President MacCracken, 1921 Jun (Box 7 [Package029_004])
    - Commencement — President MacCracken at Commencement with a child, possibly Maisry MacCracken, 1921 Jun (Box 1 [Package008_009])
    - Commencement — Sophomore marshall at Commencement, 1921 Jun (Box 9 [Package078_001])
    - Commencement — Students passing diplomas at Commencement, 1921 Jun (Box 90/91 [Box249_002])
    - Commencement — Alumnae in the commencement procession, 1922 Jun (Box 25 [package147])
    - Commencement — Class of 1922 in the commencement procession, 1922 Jun (Box 58 [package141])
    - Commencement — Class of 1922 in the commencement procession, 1922 Jun (Box 58 [package141c])
    - Commencement — Class of 1922 in the commencement procession, 1922 Jun (Box 58 [package141e])
    - Commencement — Class of 1922 in the commencement procession, 1922 Jun (Box 58 [package141g])
    - Commencement — Class of 1922 in the commencement procession, 1922 Jun (Box 58 [package141j])
    - Commencement — Class of 1922 in the commencement procession, 1922 Jun (Box 58 [package141n])
    - Commencement — Class of 1922 in the commencement procession, 1922 Jun (Box 58 [package142c])
    - Commencement — Class of 1922 in the commencement procession, 1922 Jun (Box 58 [package142e])
    - Commencement — Alumnae in the commencement procession. The marshal may be Blanch Ferry Hooker (VC 1894), 1923 Jun (Box 27 [package153d])
    - Commencement — Class of 1923 in the commencement procession, 1923 Jun (Box 19 [package106h])
    - Commencement — Class of 1923 in the commencement procession, 1923 Jun (Box 28 [package154f])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, including President MacCracken, 1923 Jun (Box 27 [package153k])
    - Commencement — Faculty procession at Commencement, including President MacCracken and Dean Ella McCaleb, 1923 Jun (Box 27 [package153b])
    - Commencement — Unidentified group in the alumnae procession, 1923 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_019])
    - Commencement — Class of 1924 in the commencement procession, 1924 Jun (Box 33/34 [Box265_007])
    - Commencement — Alumnae marshall at commencement, 1925 Jun (Box 14 [Package092_004])
    - Commencement — Class of 1925 in the commencement procession, 1925 Jun (Box 29 [package158e])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, including Caroline Furness, 1925 Jun (Box 21 [package112c])
    - Commencement — Member of the Class of 1925 at Commencement, 1925 Jun (Box 21 [package112e])
    - Commencement — Member of the Class of 1925 at Commencement, 1925 Jun (Box 21 [package112f])
    - Commencement — Member of the Class of 1925 at Commencement, 1925 Jun (Box 21 [package112g])
    - Commencement — Member of the Class of 1925 at Commencement, 1925 Jun (Box 21 [package112i])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1925 at Commencement, 1925 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_024])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1925 at Commencement, 1925 Jun (Box 3 [Package014_009])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1925 at Commencement, 1925 Jun (Box 21 [package112h])
    - Commencement — Unidentified member of the Class of 1925 at Commencement, 1925 Jun (Box 22 [package113l])
    - Commencement — Unidentified group of graduates at a Commencement, 1925-1929 (Box 33/34 [Box265_004])
    - Commencement — Class of 1926 in the commencement procession, with maids looking on from the third floor of Main Building, 1926 Jun (Box 90/91 [Box249_012])
    - Commencement — Class of 1926 in the commencement procession, with maids looking on from the third floor of Main Building, 1926 Jun (Box 90/91 [Box249_017])
    - Commencement — Class of 1926 in the commencement procession, with maids looking on from the third floor of Main Building, 1926 Jun (Box 90/91 [Box249_022])
    - Commencement — Class of 1926 passing diplomas at Commencement, 1926 Jun (Box 29 [package157j])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, with maids looking on from the third floor of Main Building, 1926 Jun (Box 90/91 [Box249_010])
    - Commencement — Class of 1927 in the commencement procession, 1927 Jun (Box 52 [Package62_007])
    - Commencement — Class of 1927 in the commencement procession, 1927 Jun (Box 52 [Package62_008])
    - Commencement — Class of 1927 in the commencement procession, 1927 Jun (Box 52 [Package63_002])
    - Commencement — Class of 1927 in the commencement procession, 1927 Jun (Box 52 [Package63_003])
    - Commencement — Class of 1927 in the commencement procession, 1927 Jun (Box 52 [Package63_008])
    - Commencement — Class of 1927 in the commencement procession, 1927 Jun (Box 52 [Package63_010])
    - Commencement — Class of 1927 in the commencement procession, 1927 Jun (Box 52 [Package63_011])
    - Commencement — Class of 1927 in the commencement procession, 1927 Jun (Box 52 [Package63_012])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1927 Jun (Box 33 [Box264_016])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1927 Jun (Box 33 [Box264_019])
    - Commencement — Fuji Nomiyama (VC 1927) at commencement with her family, 1927 Jun (Box 33/34 [Box265_021])
    - Commencement — Henry Noble MacCracken at Commencement, 1927 Jun (Box 33 [Box264_022])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1927 at Commencement, 1927 Jun (Box 33 [Box264_018])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1927 at Commencement, 1927 Jun (Box 33/34 [Box265_002])
    - Commencement — Alumnae in the commencement procession, 1928 Jun (Box 91/92 [Box250_011])
    - Commencement — Class of 1928 in the commencement procession, 1928 Jun (Box 91/92 [Box250_008])
    - Commencement — Class of 1928 in the commencement procession, 1928 Jun (Box 91/92 [Box250_009])
    - Commencement — Class of 1928 in the commencement procession, 1928 Jun (Box 91/92 [Box250_010])
    - Commencement — Class of 1928 in the commencement procession, 1928 Jun (Box 91/92 [Box250_012])
    - Commencement — Class of 1928 in the commencement procession, 1928 Jun (Box 91/92 [Box250_013])
    - Commencement — Class of 1928 in the commencement procession, 1928 Jun (Box 91/92 [Box250_014])
    - Commencement — Class of 1928 in the commencement procession, 1928 Jun (Box 91/92 [Box250_015])
    - Commencement — Class of 1928 in the commencement procession, 1928 Jun (Box 91/92 [Box250_018])
    - Commencement — Class of 1928 passing diplomas at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 25 [package147c])
    - Commencement — Class of 1928 passing diplomas at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 25 [package147d])
    - Commencement — Dorothy Goell (VC 1928) at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 23 [package116d])
    - Commencement — Dorothy Goell (VC 1928) with a man, presumably her father Charles Goell, at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 23 [package116d])
    - Commencement — Dorothy Goell (VC 1928) with her family at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 25 [package147e])
    - Commencement — Dorothy Goell (VC 1928) with her family at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 25 [package147f])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees leaving the Chapel after Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 16 [Package098_004])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees leaving the Chapel after Commencement, including Deans C. Mildred Thompson and Ella McCaleb, 1928 Jun (Box 23 [package116m])
    - Commencement — Students passing diplomas at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_023])
    - Commencement — Students passing diplomas at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 24/25 [package 121k])
    - Commencement — Students passing diplomas at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 18 [package101])
    - Commencement — Students passing diplomas at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 18 [package101b])
    - Commencement — Students passing diplomas at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 18 [package101c])
    - Commencement — Students passing diplomas at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 18 [package101d])
    - Commencement — Students passing diplomas at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 18 [package101e])
    - Commencement — Students passing diplomas at Commencement, 1928 Jun (Box 18 [package101f])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1929 with a young man, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 34 [Box266_015])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1929 with family at commencement, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 31/32 [Box262_020])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1929 with family, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_005])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1929 with family, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_019])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1929 with family, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 34 [Box266_014])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1929 with family, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 34 [Box266_016])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1929, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_010])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1929, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_011])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1929, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_023])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1929, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_024])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1929, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_025])
    - Commencement — Alumnae in the commencement procession, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 42 [Box277_005])
    - Commencement — Boxed lunch at commencement, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 32 [Box263_004])
    - Commencement — Class of 1929 in the commencement procession, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_018])
    - Commencement — Class of 1929 passing diplomas at Commencement, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_003])
    - Commencement — Dean C. Mildred Thompson in the commencement procession, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_014])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_006])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_012])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, including President MacCracken, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 33/34 [Box265_020])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1929 at Commencement, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 90/91 [Box249_023])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1929 at Commencement, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 90/91 [Box249_024])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1929 at Commencement, 1929 Jun 11 (Box 91/92 [Box250_003])
    - Commencement — Class of 1930 outside the Chapel, 1930 Jun 10 (Box 1 [Package006_006])
    - Commencement — Sophomore marshal Margaretta Miller (VC 1932) on the steps of the Chapel, 1930 Jun 10 (Box 1 [Package006_005])
    - Commencement — Trustees and President MacCracken leaving the Chapel, 1930 Jun 10 (Box 1 [Package006_007])
    - Commencement — Alumnae in the commencement procession, 1931 Jun (Box 3 [Package014_002])
    - Commencement — Alumnae in the commencement procession, 1931 Jun (Box 3 [Package014_003])
    - Commencement — Alumnae in the commencement procession, 1931 Jun (Box 23/24 [package118d])
    - Commencement — Class of 1931 in the commencement procession, 1931 Jun (Box 33 [Box264_021])
    - Commencement — Class of 1931 in the commencement procession, 1931 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_025])
    - Commencement — Class of 1931 in the commencement procession, 1931 Jun (Box 24/25 [package 121g])
    - Commencement — Class of 1931 in the commencement procession, 1931 Jun (Box 3 [Package014_005])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees leaving the Chapel after Commencement, 1931 Jun (Box 3 [Package014_007])
    - Commencement — Franklin Delano Roosevelt and Henry Noble MacCracken at Commencement, 1931 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_026])
    - Commencement — Sophomore marshall in the commencement procession, 1931 Jun (Box 3 [Package014_004])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1932 at commencement, 1932 Jun (Box 7 [Package031_006])
    - Commencement — A member of the Class of 1932 at commencement, 1932 Jun (Box 9 [Package039_003])
    - Commencement — Class of 1932 in the commencement procession, 1932 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_022])
    - Commencement — Class of 1932 in the commencement procession, 1932 Jun (Box 7 [Package031_005])
    - Commencement — Class of 1932 in the commencement procession, 1932 Jun (Box 7 [Package031_007])
    - Commencement — Class of 1932 in the commencement procession, 1932 Jun (Box 9 [Package039_002])
    - Commencement — Class of 1932 in the commencement procession, 1932 Jun (Box 9 [Package039_005])
    - Commencement — Class of 1932 in the commencement procession, 1932 Jun (Box 9 [Package039_006])
    - Commencement — Class of 1932 in the commencement procession, 1932 Jun (Box 9 [Package039_007])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1932 Jun (Box 9 [Package039_001])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1932 Jun (Box 9 [Package039_009])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1932 Jun (Box 27 [package151i])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, including President MacCracken, 1932 Jun (Box 9 [Package039_008])
    - Commencement — Members of the Class of 1932 at Commencement with family, 1932 Jun (Box 9 [Package039_004])
    - Commencement — Class of 1933 in the commencement procession, 1933 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_020])
    - Commencement — Class of 1933 in the commencement procession, 1933 Jun (Box 28 [package156])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1933 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_019])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1933 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_022])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1933 Jun (Box 22 [package114h])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, including President MacCracken, 1933 Jun (Box 28 [package156d])
    - Commencement — Sophomore marshals Susan Breul and Elizabeth Eckhart (both VC 1935) leading the Class of 1933 in the commencement procession, 1933 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_021])
    - Commencement — Sophomore marshals Susan Breul and Elizabeth Eckhart (both VC 1935) leading the Class of 1933 in the commencement procession, 1933 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_014])
    - Commencement — Class of 1934 in the commencement procession, 1934 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_021])
    - Commencement — Class of 1934 passing diplomas at Commencement, 1934 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_024])
    - Commencement — Class of 1934 passing diplomas at Commencement, 1934 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_025])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1934 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_005])
    - Commencement — Faculty and trustees in the commencement procession, 1934 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_006])
    - Commencement — Class of 1935 in the commencement procession, 1935 Jun (Box 34 [Box266_023])
    - Commencement — Class of 1935 in the commencement procession, 1935 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_013])
    - Commencement — Class of 1935 in the commencement procession, 1935 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_015])
    - Commencement — Class of 1935 in the commencement procession, 1935 Jun (Box 35 [Box267_016])